export const quiz3 = {
    topic: 'Bootstrap',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Which of the following class indicates a warning that might need attention?',
        choices: ['active','success','warning','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'warning',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following bootstrap style of button represents a contextual button for informational alert messages?',
        choices: ['btn','btn-info','btn-primary','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'btn-info',
      },
      {
        question:'Which of the following bootstrap style of button makes the button size extra small?',
        choices: ['btn-xs','btn-sm','btn-lg','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'btn-xs',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to provide a responsive fixed width container?',
        choices: ['container','container-fixed','container-fluid','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'container',
      },
      {
        question: 'How many columns are allowed in a bootstrap grid system?',
        choices: ['2','12','4','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '12',
      },
      {
        question: 'The correct syntax of creating a standard navigation bar is -',
        choices: ['<nav class="navigationbar navbar">','<nav class="navbar navbar-default">','<nav class="navbar default">','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '<nav class="navbar navbar-default">',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to create a dropdown menu?',
        choices: ['dropdown','select','select-list','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'dropdown',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to create a basic list group?',
        choices: ['list-group','list-grouped','select-list','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'list-group',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to indicate the uppercased text?',
        choices: ['text-capitalize','text-uppercase','uppercase','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'text-uppercase',
      },
      {
        question: ' Which of the following is correct method to add a success button?',
        choices: ['<button class = "btn btn-success"> success </button>','<button class = "btn button-success"> success </button>','<button class = "button btn-success"> success </button>','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '',
      },
      
    ],
  }